Guide to the Caldwell B. Esselstyn Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1945-1975; Series I; 9' (21 boxes)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1964
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Department of Health and Scientific Affairs (Box 9, Folder 221)
      See: box 18, folder 429
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of the Surgeon General (Box 9, Folder 221)
      See: box 18, folder 435
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service, 1951-1964 (Box 9, Folder 222)
      See also: box 3, folder 49
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service, National Institutes of Health, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 223)
      See also: box 14, folder 365
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Social Security Administration (Box 9, Folder 223)
    - United States Executive Office of the President (Box 9, Folder 223)
      See: box 41, folder 292
    - United States Executive Office of the President, Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 9, Folder 223)
      See: box 19, folder 463
    - V (Box 9, Folder 224)
    - Van Dyke, Frank, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 225)
    - Van Goor, Robert E. (Box 9, Folder 225)
      See: box 53, folders 37-194
    - Verhelle, Joseph (Box 9, Folder 225)
      See: box 40, folder 286
    - Vidal, Gore, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - Voorhis, H. Jerry (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - W (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - Wade, Preston (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - Whipple, Allen O., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 228)
    - Whipple (Allen O.) Surgical Society, 1957-1964 (Box 9, Folder 229)
    - White, Kerr L., 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 230)
    - Willcox, Alanson W., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 231)
    - Williams, G. Mennen, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 232)
    - Wilson, Glenn (Box 9, Folder 232)
      See: box 4, folder 71
    - Woodcock, Leonard (Box 9, Folder 232)
      See: box 40, folder 276
    - Worthington (Massachusetts) Health Association, Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 233)
    - Wynn, Ed, 1949, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - Wynn, Keenan, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - Y (Box 10, Folder 235)
    - Yale University (Box 10, Folder 235)
      See: box 14, folder 353
      See: box 48, folder 382
    - Yale University Department of Public Health, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 236)
    - Yale University Health Plan, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 237)
    - Yedidia, Avram, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 238)
      See also: box 14, folder 350
    - Z (Box 10, Folder 239)
    - Zwerdling, Miller, Klimst and Maurer (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Correspondence & Subject Files, 1964-1975
    - A (Box 10, Folder 240)
    - Administrators of Municipal Hospitals, Advisory Council, 1968 January (Box 10, Folder 241)
    - Albany Medical College of Union University, 1966, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 242)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1964-1967, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 243)
      See also: box 18, folder 437
      See also: box 15, folder 374
    - American Association of Clinic Business Managers, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 244)
    - American Association of Medical Clinics, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 245)
    - American Cancer Society, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 246)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators, Educational Assembly on Hospital Administration, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 247)
    - American College of Surgeons, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 248)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1963-1973 (Box 10, Folder 249-254)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, Conference on "After Medicare - What?", 1966 (Box 10, Folder 255)
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, New York City Central Labor Council, 1963-1964, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 256-258)
    - American Hospital Association, 1966-1968, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 259-260)
    - American Medical Association, Commission on Emergency Health Services, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 261)
    - American Medical Association, Emergency Medical Services Committee, 1967-1974 (Box 11, Folder 262)
    - American Optometric Association, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 263)
    - Appalachian Regional Hospitals, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 263)
    - Arnstein (Elizabeth R.) Fund, 1965-1967, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 264-265)
    - Arnstein, Margaret, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 266)
    - Anderson, Odin, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 267)
    - Associated Hospital Service of New York, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 267)
    - Associated Medical Schools of Greater New York (Box 11, Folder 267)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 268)
    - Ast, David, 1966-1971 (Box 11, Folder 269)
    - Austin, Edward B., 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 269)
    - Axelrod, Solomon J., 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 270)
    - Ba - Bi (Box 11, Folder 271)
    - B1 - By (Box 11, Folder 272)
    - Baehr, Francine, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 273)
    - Baehr, George, 1964-1967 (Box 11, Folder 273)
      See also: box 16, folder 393
      See also: box 19, folder 458
      See also: box 44, folder 340
    - Ball, Robert M., 1965-1967 May (Box 12, Folder 274-275)
    - Ball, Robert M., 1967 June-1973 (Box 12, Folder 276)
    - Bannon, Kenneth (Box 12, Folder 274-276)
    - Barach, Alvan L., 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 277)
    - Barr, David, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 278)
    - Bartlett, Marshall K., 1964-1973 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Bassett (Mary Imogene) Hospital (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Baumgartner, Leona (Box 12, Folder 279)
      See: box 87, folders 365-370
    - Bench, Edward C., 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Berger, Edward J., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Berkshire Farm for Boys, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 281)
    - Bigel, Jack, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 282)
    - Bingham, Jonathan, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Blair, Edwin Foster, 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 283)
      box 81, folder 311
    - Blair, Paxton (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Blue Cross-Blue Shield (Box 12, Folder 283)
    - Blue Cross of Greater New York, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 284)
    - Blue Cross of Michigan (Box 12, Folder 284)
      box 15, folder 379
    - Bluestone, E.M., 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 285)
    - Boucot-Sturgis, Kathleen, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 286)
    - Brand, Morris, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 287)
    - Breslow, Lester, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 288)
    - Brightman, I. Jay, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 289)
    - Brindle, James (Box 12, Folder 289)
      See: box 1, folder 11 box 41, folder 294
    - Briwa, Helen, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Brooks, Harold C., 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Brooks, Wayne, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 290)
    - Brown, Norton Sager, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 291)
    - Butler, Allan M., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 292)
    - Ca - Ch (Box 12, Folder 293)
    - Ch - Cr (Box 12, Folder 294)
    - Campbell, James A. (Box 12, Folder 294)
    - Carroll, Terence E. (Box 12, Folder 294)
      box 16, folder 391
    - Case, James H., Jr. (Box 12, Folder 294)
      See: box 2, folder 32
      box 4, folder 87
    - Cavanagh, Jerome P., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 295)
    - Clark, Dean A., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 295)
      box 88, folder 3
    - Clark, Henry T., Jr., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 295)
    - Clarke, Dana C., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 296)
    - Clement, Kenneth W., 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 296)
    - Cleveland Clinic (Box 12, Folder 296)
    - Coburn, Alvin F., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 297)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 297)
    - Columbia County Medical Society, 1964-1973 (Box 12, Folder 298)
      See also: box 5, folder 111
      box 9, folder 206
      box 15, folder 380
      box 32, folder 176
    - Columbia Memorial Hospital, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 299)
    - Columbia University, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 300)
    - Columbia University Alumni Conference, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 301)
    - Columbia University, Oral History Research Office, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 302)
    - Community Health Foundation (Cleveland), 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - Cooperative League of the U.S.A. (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - Cornelius, Dorothy A., 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - Cosin, L.Z., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - Crile, George, Jr., 1964-1969 (Box 13, Folder 305)
    - Cruikshank, Nelson H., 1965-1971 (Box 13, Folder 306)
    - Cutler, Norman, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 307)
    - Cutting, Cecil, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 307)
      See also: box 14, folder 349
    - D (Box 13, Folder 308)
    - Davis, Michael M. (Box 13, Folder 308)
      See: box 54, folder 48
      box 54, folder 51
      box 63, folder 146
    - Dearing, W. Palmer (Box 13, Folder 308)
      box 84, folders 331-364
    - Doody, Barbara J., 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 309)
    - Dubinsky, David, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 309)
    - E (Box 13, Folder 310)
    - Ebert, Robert H., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 311)
    - Edelman, John (Box 13, Folder 311)
    - Egan, Eleanor (Mrs. Daniel), 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 311)
    - Elsom, Katherine O., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - Elsom, Kendall A., 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - Erickson, Robert (Box 13, Folder 312)
      box 40, folder 288
    - Eron, Leonard, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - Evang, Karl, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - F (Box 13, Folder 313)
    - Falk, Isidore S., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 314)
      box 1, folder 11
    - Falk, Leslie A., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 315)
    - Family Health Program of Southern California, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 316)
    - Farrell, J. Coltrell, 1965-1971 (Box 13, Folder 317)
    - Faville, Katherine, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 318)
    - Fein, Rashi, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 318)
    - Feinstein Polyclinic, Hahnemann Medical College, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 319)
    - Feise, Richard, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 320)
    - Feldman, Louis, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 320)
    - Flaherty, John P., 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 320)
    - Fleming, Scott (Box 13, Folder 320)
    - G - Go (Box 13, Folder 321)
    - Gr - Gu (Box 13, Folder 322)
    - Gehrig, Eleanor (Mrs. Lou), 1971 (Box 13, Folder 323)
    - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1964-1969 (Box 13, Folder 323)
    - Gilbert, Benjamin and Madeline, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 323)
    - Gimbel, Elinor S., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 324)
    - Gimbel, Louis S., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 324)
    - Gimbel, S. Stinor, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 324)
    - Glasser, Melvin, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 324)
      box 41, folder 297
      box 78, folder 273
    - Goddard, Wendell, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 325)
    - Gold, Milton, 1964-1974 (Box 13, Folder 325)
      See also: box 23, folder 40
    - Gordon, Kermit, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 326)
      See also: box 68, folder 196
    - Gray, David H., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 327)
    - Greeley, David McL., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 327)
    - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 328)
    - Group Health Federation of America (Box 13, Folder 328)
    - Group Health Insurance, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 328)
    - Group Health Plan of St. Paul, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 330)
    - Group Health Planning Council of Greater Kansas City, Inc., [1974?] (Box 13, Folder 331)
    - Gundersen, Sven M., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 332)
    - Ha (Box 13, Folder 333)
    - He - Hu (Box 13, Folder 334)
    - Haight, Eric H., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 335)
      See also: box 12, folder 281
      box 20, folder 475-476
    - Hanlon, John (Box 13, Folder 335)
    - Harmer, Ruth, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 335)
    - Health Information Foundation (Box 13, Folder 335)
      See: box 11, folder 267
    - Hess, Arthur, 1965-1966 July-Aug, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 336-337)
    - Hilleboe, Herman E., 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Holmes, Hillary H., 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Howard University, Conference on the Health Status of the Negro, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 339)
    - Hudson River Regional Mental Health Planning Committee, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 340)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 341)
    - I (Box 14, Folder 342)
    - Ingraham, Hollis, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 343)
      See also: box 48, folder 384
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 14, Folder 343)
    - Ipsen, Johannes, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 344)
    - J (Box 14, Folder 345)
    - Jacobson, George W. (Box 14, Folder 345)
      box 53, folder 43
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 346)
    - Johnson, Robert L., 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 347)
    - Johnson, Robert R., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 347)
    - K (Box 14, Folder 348)
    - Kaiser Foundation, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 349)
    - Kaiser Foundation, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 350)
    - Kaiser Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 351)
      See also: box 19, folder 455
      box 39, folders 274-310
      box 78, folders 267-305
    - Keene, Clifford (Box 14, Folder 351)
    - Kerr, Lorin E., 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 352)
      box 11, folder 261
      box 50, folders 1-34
      box 59, folder 99
    - Kerr, Walter S., Jr., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Kingren, Gibson (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Kiphuth, Delaney, 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Kiphuth, Robert J., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 353)
    - Kirkland, Lane, 1964, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Kissick, William, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Kivel, Raymond, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 354)
    - Klem, Margaret C., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - Knowles, John, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - Koplin, Allen, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - Kornfeld, Allan (Box 14, Folder 355)
    - La - Ler (Box 14, Folder 356)
    - Les - Lu (Box 14, Folder 357)
    - L.S.I. Service Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 358)
    - Larimore, Granville W., 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 359)
    - Larkin, Vincent DePaul (Box 14, Folder 359)
    - Lee, Russel V., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 360)
      See also: box 1, folders 8-9
    - Lipton, Martin (Box 14, Folder 360)
    - Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 361)
    - Ma (Box 14, Folder 362)
    - Me (Box 14, Folder 363)
    - Mi - My (Box 14, Folder 364)
    - McCabe, Frank W., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - McCabe, John C., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - McCormack, James (Box 14, Folder 365)
      box 42, folders 311-374
    - McCree, Wade H. (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - McGuinness, Aims (Box 14, Folder 365)
      See: box 16, folder 397
    - MacLeod, Gordon K. (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - Masur, Jack, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Mattison, Berwyn (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - May, George A., Jr., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Mayer, Vera (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Means, James Howard, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Medical Administrators Conference, 1964-1974 (Box 15, Folder 367-371)
    - Medical Economics, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 372-373)
    - Medical Foundation of Bellaire, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 374)
      See also: box 3, folder 53
      box 64, folders 162-163
    - Medical Society of the State of New York, Committee on Accident and Injury Prevention, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 375)
      See also: box 7, folder 167
    - Medicare (Box 15, Folder 375)
      box 64, folder 156
    - Melamed, Isidor, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - Meltzer, Marvin, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 376)
      box 47, folder 368
    - Metcalf, George R., 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - Michigan Governor's Action Committee on Health Care, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - Michigan Health Maintenance Organization Plans, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - Michigan Hospital Service, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - Michigan State Board of Registration in Medicine, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - Michigan State Medical Society, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - Michigan, University of, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 383)
    - Mott, Frederick D., 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 384)
      box 60, folder 110
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 385)
    - Myers, Beverlee A., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 386)
    - Myers, Glynn (Box 16, Folder 386)
    - N (Box 16, Folder 387)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 388)
    - National Council on the Aging, Inc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 389)
    - National Foundation of Health, Welfare and Pension Funds, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 390)
    - National Institutes on Rehabilitation and Health Services, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 391)
    - Neiman, I.S., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 392)
    - Nelson, John A., 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 392)
      See also: box 58, folder 95
    - Nelson, Russell A., 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 392)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 393-394)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, Committee on Medical Education, Subcommittee on Group Practice, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 395)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, Committee on Special Studies, 1967-1968 April (Box 16, Folder 396-397)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, Committee on Special Studies, Subcommittee on Social Policy for Health Care, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 398)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1966-1967 February (Box 16, Folder 399)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1967 March-November (Box 17, Folder 400-401)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 402)
    - New York State Department of Health (Box 17, Folder 402)
      See: box 5, folder 112
      box 6, folder 136
    - New York State Department of Health, Health Manpower Group, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 403)
    - New York State Department of Health, Health Resources Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 404)
    - New York State Department of Health, Weekly Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 405)
    - New York State Employees Retirement System, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 406)
    - New York State Interdepartmental Health Resources Board (Box 17, Folder 406)
    - New York State Joint Hospital Survey and Planning Commission, Albany Regional Hospital Planning Council (Box 17, Folder 406)
    - New York State Society of Internal Medicine, Remuneration Study, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 407)
    - New York State Workmen's Compensation Board, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 408)
    - O (Box 17, Folder 409)
    - Olson, Kenneth B., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 410)
    - O'Meara, Edward S., 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 410)
    - P (Box 17, Folder 411)
    - Palo Alto Clinic (Box 17, Folder 411)
    - Peterson, Osler L., 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 412)
    - Physicians Forum Inc., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 412)
    - Pillsbury, Philip W., 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 413)
    - Pomeroy, Robert Watson, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 413)
    - Preventive Medicine Institute, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 414)
    - Public Health Association of New York City, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 415)
    - Putnam County Medical Society, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 416)
    - Ra - Rog, 1964-1974 (Box 17, Folder 417)
    - Rom - Ry (Box 17, Folder 418)
    - Ravitz, Melvin, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 419)
    - Ray, G. Stewart, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 419)
    - Reader, George, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 420)
    - Reeves, Arthur, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 420)
    - Reuther, Walter P., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 421)
      See also: box 40, Folder 282
    - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 17, Folder 421)
    - Robbins, C.L., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Robertson, Alexander (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Roemer, Milton I., 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Rose, Alfred L., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Rose, Milton, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 422)
    - Rutgers Community Health Plan, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 423)
    - Sa - Sc (Box 17, Folder 424)
    - Se - Sl (Box 17, Folder 425)
    - Sm - Sw (Box 17, Folder 426)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Scholdager, Rolf, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Segadelli, Louis (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Segal, Martin E., 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Seidman, Bert, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 427)
    - Seubold, Frank, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 427)
      See also: box 48, folders 385-403
    - Shadid, Michael, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - Sheps, Cecil G., 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - Sherman, Samuel, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - Shoemaker, Richard (Box 18, Folder 428)
      box 80, folder 294
    - Shortlifte., Ernest C. (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - Siebert, Jane (Box 18, Folder 428)
    - Silver, George A., 1964-1971 (Box 18, Folder 429)
    - Smith, Kay (Mrs. Ralph), 1964, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 430)
    - Snake, Albert W., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 431)
    - Somers, Herman M., 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 432)
      See also: box 15, folder 373
    - Spock, Anne, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 433)
    - Spock, Benjamin, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 433)
    - Stark, Nathan J., 1966-1968, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 434)
      See also: box 47, folder 369
    - Stewart, William H., 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 435)
    - Stoeckle, John D., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 436)
    - Straus, Donald B., 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 437)
    - T (Box 18, Folder 438)
    - Terris, Milton (Box 18, Folder 438)
      box 20, folder 476
    - Trese, John A., 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 439)
      See also: box 42, folder 304
    - Trussell, Ray E., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 440)
    - U (Box 18, Folder 441)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 18, Folder 441)
    - United Auto Workers, Health Care Benefits, 1964 March - 1967 (Box 18, Folder 442-443)
    - United Auto Workers, Leadership Studies Center, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 444)
    - United Auto Workers, Region 1-D Spring Leadership Institute, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 445)
    - United Auto Workers, Summer School Program, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 446)
    - United Auto Workers, Union Health Services, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 447)
    - United Mine Workers of America (Box 18, Folder 448)
      See also: box 6, folder 130
      box 13, folder 309
      box 13, folder 315
      box 14, folder 352
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 18, Folder 448)
      box 7, folder 180
      box 9, folder 209
      box 9, folder 231
      box 12, folder 275-277
      box 12, folder 297
      box 13, folder 336-337
      box 16, folder 386
    - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Bureau of Health Services, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 449)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Department of Health and Scientific Affairs, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 450)
      See also: box 18, folder 429
    - United States, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 451)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, National Institutes of Health, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 452)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of the Secretary, National Conference on Medical Costs, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 453-454)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of the Surgeon General (Box 18, Folder 453-454)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service (Box 18, Folder 453-454)
      See: box 3, folder 49
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service, Labor Seminar on "Consumer Health Services", 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 455)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Public Health Service, National Conference on Group Practice, 1967 October 19-21 (Box 19, Folder 456)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Public Health Service, Partnership for Health - Public Law 89-749, 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 457)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Social and Rehabilitation Service, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 458)
    - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Social Security Administration (Box 19, Folder 458)